<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Webspider</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="prompt_email">Email Id</string>
    <string name="prompt_username">User Name</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="sign_in">SIGNIN</string>
    <string name="register">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="loading">Please wait...</string>
    <string name="show">show</string>
    <string name="hide">Hide</string>
    <string name="forgotpassword">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="donthaveaccount">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="signup">Signup</string>
    <string name="verification_text">We need to text to you a confirmation code to get started.</string>
    <string name="why">Why?</string>
    <string name="prompt_phonenumer">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="sentotp">SEND OTP</string>
    <string name="resendotp">Resend OTP</string>
    <string name="prompt_enterotp">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="signup_caps">SIGNUP</string>
    <string name="change">Change</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="call">Call</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="like">Like</string>
    <string name="liked">Liked</string>
    <string name="addtowishlist">Add to wishlist</string>
    <string name="removefromwishlist">Remove from wishlist</string>
    <string name="totalviews">Total Views :</string>
    <string name="phone">Phone</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="contactperson">Contact Person</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="address">1st Floor , Moti Nagar, Karmik Nagar, Dhanbad</string>
    <string name="websitelink">http://www.websspider.com/</string>
    <string name="emaillink">support@websspider.com</string>
    <string name="contactus">CONTACT US</string>
    <string name="home">HOME</string>
    <string name="aboutus">ABOUT US</string>
    <string name="bachao">BACHAO</string>
    <string name="alreadyaccount">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="login_small">Login</string>
    <string name="aboutwebspider">ABOUT WEBSPIDER</string>
    <string name="aboutus_lontext">“WEB SPIDER has every small town solutions.” A WEB SPIDER Helps in bridging the gap between buyers and sellers by providing relevant information.WEB SPIDER helps not only Search, but you can get instant information about shops and services around you. Search Anything, Anywhere, Anytime by using WEB SPIDER. Here in WEB SPIDER you get Phone Numbers, email, Addresses, Deals, Discount, Reviews, portfolio, and works as a one stop solution for all your daily needs. No more planning, just search, get up and go - Easily pick shops and services by category or locations. Buyers and sellers meat together in WEB SPIDER.</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate</string>
    <string name="vendorname">Vendor Shop Name</string>
    <string name="typevendorname">Type vendor name</string>
    <string name="vendorcontactpersonname">Vendorcontact person name</string>
    <string name="typevendorcontactpersonname">Type vendor contact person name</string>
    <string name="vendorpersoncontactnumber">Vendor contact number</string>
    <string name="vendoremail">Vendor email</string>
    <string name="vendorwebsiteurllink">Vendor website email eg:- (http://www.websspider.com/)</string>
    <string name="vendorwebsiteurl">Vendor website email </string>
    <string name="vendorlocation">Vendor shop location</string>
    <string name="vendordetails">Vendor Details</string>
    <string name="productdetails">Product Details</string>
    <string name="productname">Product name</string>
    <string name="producsortdesc">Product short description</string>
    <string name="produclondesc">Product long description</string>
    <string name="coupancodename">Coupan code</string>
    <string name="typeselectcategory">Type/Select Category</string>
    <string name="loading_location">getting location, please wait</string>
    <string name="submitvendordetails">Submit Vendor Details</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="logout_big">LOGOUT</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="dob">DOB</string>
    <string name="gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="myprofile">MY PROFILE</string>
    <string name="update">UPDATE</string>
    <string name="loginType">Logintype</string>
    <string name="gplus">gplus</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="is_signin">issign</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="linked">linked</string>
    <string name="normal">Normal</string>


    <string name="facebook_app_id">1298961933559690</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1298961933559690</string>
    <string name="fb">fb</string>
    <string name="social">social</string>
    <string name="chooselocation">Choose Your Location</string>
    <string name="popularcity">Popular Cities</string>
    <string name="serach">Serach</string>
    <string name="flight">Flights</string>
    <string name="milionome">My Holidays</string>
    <string name="rblindia">Recharge</string>
    <string name="hotdeals">Hot Deals</string>
    <string name="popularcities">Popular Cities</string>
    <string name="aboutus_content"><![CDATA[Web Spider is one of the fastest growing Classified Company, which is based Dhanbad very soon we were in across India. The Company assists the Business Enterprises under all the categories in their business promotion by publishing their Classifieds & Hot Deals on its website. In this way, Web Spider also meets the needs of the local residents and those outsiders who come for a short stay or to settle down for a long. The Company provides Local Search Engine (City wise). It helps the users in finding out the suppliers of the products and services that meet their needs. The website also helps the business entities that are looking forward to give a boost to their business by way of lead generation. The portal of the Company works as a platform for the customers/consumers and the suppliers enabling them to connect to each other and arrive at deals. Since its inception, a fairly large number of business entities have benefited a lot and seen a tremendous growth in their business by listing on the website of Web Spider, www.websspider.com. Today; it is not only one of the fastest blooming but also amongst largest classified portals in India.  The Company is managed by the well qualified Board of Directors who is highly dedicated to the welfare cause of the society. The Company has on its rolls, a team of talented & highly skilled IT professionals with several years of experience in client servicing.  Its website, the online advertisement platform of the Company is highly Responsive and a Mobile website. It\'s also available in Mobile Application Mode which can be downloaded on all the Smart Phones.  On the platter of this highly beneficial and unique web application, we offer pocket-friendly offers and packages. With a wide array of services it offers, the company also posts irresistible deals. Besides listing classifieds, the Company also publishes attractive HOT DEALS and Coupons offered by the business enterprises under the categories of Food & Drink, Entertainment, Salon & Spa, Fitness & Hobby, Hotel & Travel, Health & Doctor, Service Deals, Product Deals, Education and Real Estate etc. Our Hot Deals segment not only helps these specially categorized entities grow speedily, but also build a long-lasting relationship with their customers.  Web Spider always endeavours to provide its valued customers with a high quality of service. Besides the online advertisement, the Company also brings out The Web Spider, a Hand Book of Coupons of Hot Deals. This Hand Book is published in Cities Wise Editions and goes a long way in building lasting B2C relations and sustainable business growth of the advertisers.  We can also be categorized as a business directory which provides to the customers, the classified information about sourcing numerous products and services. This online marketplace also provides B2C & B2B (local level business-to-business transactions) platforms to the SMEs, businessmen and to the customers who are looking for various options available to them in a particular product which they would like to buy. The company plans to diversify its business activities and will be very soon, entering into the line of various online bookings and deals as well.  As the name suggests, it attracts Web Spider of people who wish to buy, sell or avail the services of the professionals like Doctors, Architects, Engineers, CAs , Lawyers,  and someone who is looking for a Hotel for a short stay or accommodation to rent. In short, it is one of the largest portals not only for businessmen, SMEs, but also for the individuals where one can source, sell or get needed products, services and information.  We stand out among the countless mobile applications. Owing to our specialized services which we offer in the areas of Hotel & Tourism, Franchises, Real Estate, Education, Healthcare, Medicine, the venue for various occasions and many other sectors, we provide information on almost everything which is just a click away from the consumers.  Vision  We believe in making the life of our clients and users easy in todays fast pace. To provide all services to the users under one umbrella is what we focus on. We are constantly improving and working on providing the best service to our users. We intend to make a significant contribution in transforming their lifestyle a smart one from the traditional way of shopping and acquiring. We believe in deep and stable collaborations for achieving long-term goals as we are here to build relationships with our users.  Mission:   The genesis of our company starts with our mission. We aim to spread optimism, create the value of people & time and to simplify things in the existing complex lifestyle. The mission is simple, i.e. to connect the people who could be useful and beneficial to each other.]]></string>
	<string name="termsandconditions"><![CDATA[These Terms govern the use of this website which is owned & managed by Web Spider Please read the terms carefully. By using this website or contacting suppliers of products or service providers from this website, the user agrees to be bound by all of the terms and conditions of this agreement. In case you do not accept any of the terms, then please do not make any type of correspondence with the advertisers. These terms and conditions include amendments as on this day or to be made in the future and also any other rules or policies that may be posted on the website from time to time. \n1.  Entirety of Terms & Conditions:  By accessing or using this website, the users give their consent and are agreeing to these Terms of Use for the users, together with the Privacy Policy, Infringement Policy & other Terms published on www.websspider.com, in their entirety without any deviation. All these documents are read together & constitute the entire terms and conditions applicable to use this Website. \n2. Nature of Service Provided:  Web Spider is an Online Advertising Company and publishes on its website,  business classified ads, deals & sale offers of the advertisers. It offers its platform to the advertisers and the users for B2C transactions. Web Spider does not claim any charges, commission or brokerage from the users/consumers who avail the service for sourcing various products or services advertised on the website. Web Spider does not have any direct relationship with any transaction between the Consumer and Seller or Service Provider. \n3. Limited Rights to Use Website:   Web Spider reserves all the rights for granting permission to use this website and grants the users, limited rights to use the content and materials displayed on the Website for non-commercial purposes. In any case, the user shall not copy, reproduce, transmit, distribute, or create derivative works of such content or information without express written permission by Web Spider  \n4. Customer Solicitation:   The Regd. Users of this website are impliedly consenting and authorizing the Business Relations, Sales & Marketing and Tele Caller Team members to make them the telephonic calls or send SMS or e-mails. \n5. Compliance of Law:  The user agrees to fully comply with the Law in force in India, as applicable to the use of the Internet or Web Services and any other contractual terms which govern the use of the Internet and/or Web Services. The user agrees that he will not use the website for any type of illegal purposes. Where the user is using the Services outside India or in a Foreign Country, he agrees to comply with those specific laws prevailing in the country where the Service is used or as applicable to him in any of his geographical locations.\n6. Prohibitions & Restrictions:  In any case, the user shall not upload to the Web Spiders websites or transmit to it, any IT codes, harmful virus, Trojan Horse, web bugs or any file, or program that may damage or is intended to damage or hijack the operation of any hardware or software. He shall not, otherwise use it to design and/or develop for sale to 3rd parties, the contents, pictures, and videos. \n7. Intellectual Property Rights:  This Web site displays information, advertisements, sale offers and other marketing materials that have been provided by the Advertisers & Merchants. This Web site offers information, both directly and through indirect links to third-party websites. Web Spider also displays on its website, such information which is gathered from other sources as well.  To the extent that Web Spider creates the content for the website, its Rights related to such content are entirely protected by the Provisions of Copy Right Act, Trade Mark Act, Indian Intellectual Property Law and the provisions and Rules framed by the other International Organisations which govern the matter. Therefore, any unauthorised use of the material shall violate Copyright, Trademark, or any other law in force from time to time. \n8. Third Party Links  With the motive and for the sole purpose of convenience to the users, Web Spider provides or may provide in future, links to third-party websites. Web Spider does not endorse the contents of any such third-party websites that carry the link to its website. Web Spider shall not be responsible for the content of those third party websites, or any damage that may result from the access to such third-party websites. The user shall access those third-party websites through the links, at his risk. \n9. Liability of Web Spider: \na) Web Spider shall not be liable for the truthfulness or accuracy of the content information displayed on the website. \nb) It does not take any responsibility or guarantees, the standards of the quality or performance of the products listed on its website. \nc) Web Spider does not assume any liability for the loss sustained by the users or third parties due to the use of the website. \nd) It will not be liable for a failure of the website to operate with any other programs, even if  Web Spider has been cautioned on this point. \ne) The user will use the website entirely at his risk.]]></string>
    <string
        name="privacy"><![CDATA[PRIVACY POLICY  Web Spider, from time to time, frames the policy and methods as to how it collects the information from the Advertisers/ Merchants / Listers and uses it for publication on the website which is visible to all those who may visit the website.  This Privacy Policy discloses as to how Web Spider uses and protects the information which it collects from the Advertisers/ Merchant/Listers for publication on the website.  Web Spider is, and will always remain committed to ensure the Privacy of all such information provided by the Advertisers/ Merchants/ Listers which is not required to be displayed on the website or which has not to be the part of classified &/or deals advertisement.  However, Web Spider has no control and cannot restrict or prevent the users or visitors to the website from accessing the information displayed published on it.  We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information related to our valuable customers is protected and maintained.   Web Spider reserves all the rights to add, amend or delete any part of this Privacy  Policy. \n1. Procedural points that outline our privacy policy:  \na) Web Spider will identify the purposes for which personal and business information of the Advertiser/Lister is being collected. The information so collected will be used for fulfilling those purposes only.  \nb) We will collect information of the Advertiser/Lister only by lawful means.  \nc) Well share the collected information with the Advertiser/Lister. If required and where appropriate, the information will be used with the knowledge or consent of the Advertiser/Lister. \nd) Well take every care that business and personal data of the Advertiser/.Lister is essential and relevant to the purposes for which it has to be used.  \ne) Well take every care that business and personal information of the Advertiser/Lister is correct, accurate and up-to- date to the best of our knowledge and belief.  \nf) We will take reasonable steps to protect the information by security safeguards against misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.  \n2. Purpose for which we collect the information:  Web Spider is an Online Classified Company & to display on this website the classified ads and sale promotion offers of its customers who are business enterprises and service providers, it collects all such information which is necessary for this purpose.  \n3. Type of Information that we collect: Web Spider collects the following material information from its Advertisers/  Merchants/Listers:  \na) Name & Address of the Business Enterprises or Service Providers.  \nb) Nature of business, products or services offered to the consumers. \nc) Names of contact persons.  \nd) Complete contact details for the convenience of the users/consumers.  \ne) Postal Codes & other demographic information.  \nf) Any other information that may be related to the publication of the classifieds and is necessary.  \n4. How do we use this information?  Besides displaying the information on the website by way of classifieds & / or Deals/ or Sale Offers, the information so collected is used for the following purposes:  \na) For our internal Data Base  \nb) For improving the quality of service we offer to the Advertisers & the End Users, both.  \nc) For customization of the Classifieds as per needs of the advertisers.  \nd) For sending SMS, E-mails, digital marketing and for posting on social websites namely Face Book, Twitter, Pintrest, Blogger, etc.  \ne) For the purpose to contact the Advertisers.  \n5. Use of Cookies:  We use certain cookies that help us monitor as to which of the web pages are useful and which require modifications in order to customize the web pages according to the specific needs of the advertisers. In any case, we do not have any access to the data that you do not want to share with us.  \n6. Protection against un-authortised use:  We are committed to protect and secure the information provided to us against any un- authorised use, misuse or illegal use.  \n7. Links & Hyper-Links:  The website also contains or may contain in future, certain links & hyper-links to the other websites. The sole purpose of providing such links is to enable the Advertisers visit the other website of interest. Those other websites are not covered under the Privacy Policy because we cannot exercise any control over the content information of those Third Party Websites.  \n8. Contents-Information is visible to the public:  This website can be visited and viewed by any person who so ever may like. There is no control over the website by way of Log On and Pass Word technique. Therefore, we cannot control or restrict any person from accessing or viewing the website. The content information published on this website is visible to all the visitors.]]></string>
	<string name="chooser_title">Webspider</string>
</resources>
